enjoythepics.com 2015-03-25

# Privacy Policy - Enjoy The Pics

Adverts

style="display:inline-block;width:468px;height:15px"  
data-ad-client="ca-pub-8423824671108420"  
data-ad-slot="3206899703">  
At [EnjoyThePics.com](http://www.enjoythepics.com/ "EnjoyThePics"), we are committed to protecting your privacy. Please read our privacy policy carefully and **[contact us](http://www.enjoythepics.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us")** if you have any questions or concerns. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by EnjoyThePics.com. Use of our Website assumes you have read, understand, and agree with our privacy policy.

**Third-Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personal information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third-Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize “cookies” on your browser. We have no access to or control over the cookies used by our third-party advertisers.

**Google Advertising Cookies**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google’s use of the [DART](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx "DART Privacy") cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html "Google's Privacy Policy").

**Interest Based Advertising:**

Google Adsense serves ads based on the interest of the user/visitor. If you visit Technical sites very regularly which uses adsense, then you will be grouped into “Tech enthusiast” category. This is called Interest based advertising and to achieve this, they collect some data from visits which do not include your name, mail id, phone number, address or any such details..

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. EnjoyThePics.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. So feel safe during your stay on the site.

Adverts

style="display:inline-block;width:336px;height:280px"  
data-ad-client="ca-pub-8423824671108420"  
data-ad-slot="3944946983">
